https://www.thevintageposter.com/about-us/privacy-policy/

MenuFind a PosterFind a poster by category
Search for a poster »
New Acquisitions
See all new acquisitions > CloseNew AcquisitionsFeatured PostersFeatured PostersSee all featured posters >
CloseSpecialsAbout UsWhat Our Customers SayContact UsSee the GalleryPrivacy PolicyHow to Buy a Vintage Poster from Us CloseServicesProfessional FramingLinen Backing CloseBlog
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you place an order, or register on the site.  This information is never shared with, or sold to, a third party.
When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes.
Like many websites, we use “cookies” to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the “Do we use ‘cookies’?” section below for information about cookies and how we use them.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect in the following ways:
To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
To quickly process your transactions.
If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the “How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?” section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and ‘members-only’ content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.
How do we protect visitor information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted.    Your credit card information and number is processed separately by authorize.net .    Your credit card number for on-line sales is never provided nor available to The Vintage Poster.
Do we use “cookies”?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won’t have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.
Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. The term “outside parties” does not include TheVintagePoster.com. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.
How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?
To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the “My Account” section. Please note that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in production.
To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the “My Account” section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.
Third party links
In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).
Changes to our policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on November 20, 2010.
Questions and feedback
We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue.
Online Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.
Your consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Follow us
About UsWhat Our Customers SayContact UsSee the GalleryHow to Buy a Vintage Poster from UsShipping and ReturnsPrivacy PolicyTerms of ServicePoster Search
Poster Categories
Featured Posters
Specials
New Acquisitions
Services
Find a Poster
Reproduction Posters
About Us
Contact Info The Vintage Poster
1492 S. Coast Hwy.
Laguna Beach, CA 92651
800-558-7552
Local: 949-376-7422
Gallery BlogProtected: Vintage Poster Linen Backing and RestorationAugust 31, 2018There is no excerpt because this is a protected post.Vintage Posters – Valuable Art – Appreciating Art Values.February 25, 2017CHAMPAGNE DE ROCHEGRE. Rare original  1902, Leonetto Cappiello,  turn of …The Vintage Poster:
Best Antique Vintage Poster Shop and Custom Framing GalleryOctober 26, 2016Welcome to The Vintage Poster:  The West Coast’s largest antique vintage …CUSTOM FRAMING for ORIGINAL VINTAGE POSTERSOctober 18, 2016    The Vintage Poster Gallery of Laguna Beach Custom …
Social
Subscribe
Newsletter Subscribe
First Name
*
Last Name
*
Email
If you are human, leave this field blank.
Poster Dealers Association
Back to Top
Pin It on Pinterest
